<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tybeard</title>
    <link>https://tybearder.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tybeard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, theme made by Weru and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:52:59 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tybearder.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Echo of the Silence</title>
      <link>https://tybearder.com/post/echo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 13:34:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tybearder.com/post/echo/</guid>
      <description>Imagine that you are walking along the main street of your City. In the midst of the crowd, with the caresses of the tangled sounds of people shielded by yours headphones, playing to the rhythm of your mood. The sun is setting and softening the wrinkles of the buildings that embrace the sides of the street. The lights of the shops, hidden by the arcades, decorate the street like a Christmas tree and fill it with smells and perfumes, as if the one the of the woman who has just touched you, without even noticing, armed with black glasses and a quick step, was not enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams</title>
      <link>https://tybearder.com/post/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 13:32:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tybearder.com/post/dreams/</guid>
      <description>There is one frightened, who speaks softly under his breath. There is one forgotten that, banging on every wall, wandering, tries to get back on the right path. There is one strong who, screaming in the face of others tries to drive them away, so as to remain alone in the whole territory, conquering nothingness. There is a small one that shines like the full moon on a clear summer night and there is one big, cumbersome, colorless, still, it seems almost fake, useless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycle</title>
      <link>https://tybearder.com/post/cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 13:31:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tybearder.com/post/cycle/</guid>
      <description>At the beginning, everything is nothing. Everything gets built by itself, above its roots, which grow and spread even in hostile land, in lands where nothing has managed to grow before now.
It’s an eternal process, a process that happens faster than a flash of lightning. It’s something you stand by, terribly hoping to be part of that process, but you’re so focused on who knows what you do not realize it’s already happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Old Lady With The Red Lipstick</title>
      <link>https://tybearder.com/post/turin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 13:16:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tybearder.com/post/turin/</guid>
      <description>I expected a cold city. I expected an austere city. I expected a city, still in its desired nobility. I expected a city that screams speeches without arguments. I expected a city that would look at you with a eye of superiority, from top to bottom, almost snubbing you. I expected a detached city, almost annoyed to have you there, on its streets. I expected a city that would make you walk on its way but didn’t want to get dirty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventure Of Bì: an untold story</title>
      <link>https://tybearder.com/post/biadventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tybearder.com/post/biadventure/</guid>
      <description>Act One: Wanderer Once upon a time there was Bì, a little red shiny plastic puppet, different from everyone else.
Bì lived in the world of humans even if he was nothing but human. Bì was named in this way to remind himself he was not wanted, he just happened.
Bì was different from everyone else, he was heartless, but still he can love, suffer, cry, and be kind. Bì was headless, but still he can reason, think and behave wisely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://tybearder.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 11:54:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tybearder.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Hello, glad to see you again.
This blog it&amp;rsquo;s not the only thing I have to keep us in touch. There are plenty of social where you get to know me more.
First of all, my personal site: andreabredice.dev You can know more about my job and about my little funny coding project, you know, code and write it involves the same creativity.
But let&amp;rsquo;s be more social:
 Medium : the most important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Tybeard</title>
      <link>https://tybearder.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tybearder.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, World!
I am Andrea, 26 y.o. guy from the north of Italy. Welcome to Tybearder. What the heck is this?! Let me explain.
Let&amp;rsquo;s begin with the name. It&amp;rsquo;s a fusion between typo, beard and reader or writer, depend of the figure you will play, of course I truly hope you can be my reader. Why? Well, it&amp;rsquo;s a blog, so I type and you read. And the beard? I&amp;rsquo;ve been having a beard since 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>